{
    "subject": "resource/Aselin_Debison",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Canada",
    "human_readable": "Aselin Debison's hometown is Canada.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886606931686401,
            "question": "Is Canada considered Aselin Debison's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9480108618736267,
            "question": "Is Aselin Debison originally from Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9227373600006104,
            "question": "What is the name of Aselin Debison's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9184505939483643,
            "question": "What country is Aselin Debison's hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7520210146903992,
            "question": "Where is Aselin Debison from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.663318395614624,
            "question": "Where was Aselin Debison raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6239172220230103,
            "question": "Where did Aselin Debison grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5729634165763855,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Aselin Debison?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3997707962989807,
            "question": "Can you tell me Aselin Debison's place of birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37798741459846497,
            "question": "Aselin Debison calls which country home?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Aselin Debison's hometown is Canada.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8165_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me Aselin Debison's place of birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8165_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Aselin Debison?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8165_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Aselin Debison grow up?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8165_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8165_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8165_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8165_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8165_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8165_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8165_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8165_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8165_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8165_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8165_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents mention Aselin Debison being from Canada, they specify her hometown as Glace Bay, Nova Scotia, not just Canada in general. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Aselin Debison was born in Glace Bay, Nova Scotia, Canada and graduated from educational institutions in Canada. Additionally, she is referred to as a Canadian singer. Therefore, the information supports that her hometown is Canada."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"no\"}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Aselin Debison's hometown is Glace Bay, Nova Scotia, Canada, which is a specific location within Canada, not just Canada as a whole.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several pieces of text state her hometown is Glace Bay, Nova Scotia, Canada.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}